lasvegasdirect.com 2019-06-24

# Las Vegas Direct Privacy Policy | Las Vegas Direct

Las Vegas Direct has established and carried out information handling practices for [www.LasVegasDirect.com](http://www.lasvegasdirect.com/) that we truly believe are consistent with the highest standards and best procedures of organizations doing business on the Internet today. This privacy policy describes the procedures that apply to LasVegasDirect.com, including:

  * The information we collect about you
  * When and how we collect that information
  * What may happen to that information

Below is a detailed description of LasVegasDirect.com’s information handling.

**Cookies**  
Some information is collected automatically every time you visit LasVegasDirect.com. Las Vegas Direct collects information about your visit and assigns you a “cookie” (a unique text file) when you visit LasVegasDirect.com. You do not provide this information – it is collected automatically as a means of supporting your visit to our site. We use cookies on our site to collect session data for several purposes to personalize and improve your individual viewing experience. For example, we use cookies to keep track of your use of our site, gather data to improve the content, and provide information that may be of interest to you. This cookie is completely anonymous and contains no personal information about the user. You can always decide to not receive a cookie by enabling your Web browser to refuse cookies or prompt you before accepting a cookie. Be advised that, by refusing to accept cookies, you may not be able to access services or reservation tools provided by LasVegasDirect. 

**What information we collect**

**Personal Information**  
LasVegasDirect.com collects your personal information that you specifically and voluntarily provide. personal information includes information that can identify you as a specific individual, such as name, phone number, email address, and address. In order to fulfill travel requests, it is necessary for us to collect personal information including the previously mentioned information. Declining to provide this information will impede your access to all sections of LasVegasDirect.com and your ability to book reservations on LasVegasDirect.com.

On all Las Vegas Direct pages that request personal information, we explicate what information is required in order to provide you with the requested product or service.

**Payment Information**  
By using the LasVegasDirect, you will be able to book, reserve or purchase travel services or accommodations. To use these services, you must provide payment information to us including credit card specifics like card number and type, issuing bank, expiration date, cardholder name and billing address. This information will only be required in as a consequence of requesting reservation services.

**Activity Information**  
Las Vegas Direct reserves the right to collect technical information from your computer each time you request a Web page. This information is accessed from your Web browser and may include your Web browser type and version, operating system, IP address, and screen resolution.

Las Vegas Direct may also track your actions on LasVegasDirect.com including which pages are viewed, length of time spent on each page, and referrer Web site. This information is used to make improvements content, navigation, and potential marketing targets.

We use Remarketing with Google Analytics to advertise online. What this means is that we may collect information once you visit us in the form of a cookie and later display an ad on Google’s Display Ad Network to market relevant ads to you about us. Third-party vendors, including Google, may show relevant ads on sites across the Internet based on your browsing behavior on our site. Las Vegas Direct and third-party vendors, including Google, use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to inform, optimize, and serve ads based on someone’s past visits to your website.

**Disclosure**  
Las Vegas Direct does not rent or sell your personal information including name, email address, phone number or any credit card or billing information.

Las Vegas Direct only provides information about travel, either reserved or purchased, on LasVegasDirect.com to third parties that provide services or functions on our behalf. Our service providers need your personal and credit card information, to process and confirm your travel reservation. These providers will disclose your personal information to the necessary suppliers whose products you have purchased. Like any other travel agent, this information must be shared with our travel suppliers to confirm your reservation and travel preferences. Although Las Vegas Direct offers travel products from suppliers that are reputable companies, we have not placed limitations on these suppliers from using or disclosing your information without your permission. Therefore, we encourage you to review the privacy policies of any travel suppliers whose products you have purchased on LasVegasDirect.com. In addition, these travel suppliers may also contact you as necessary to obtain additional information about your confirmed reservation.

There may be pages throughout LasVegasDirect.com that link to other Web sites that do not operate under LasVegasDirect’s privacy policy. Once you leave the LasVegasDirect.com domain, our privacy policy no longer applies. We recommend that you examine the privacy policies for all third party Web sites to understand their procedures for obtaining, using, and sharing your information.

Las Vegas Direct may be required by law to disclose information you have provided in purchasing travel products and services. Las Vegas Direct may also disclose information against someone who may pose as a threat to LasVegasDirect’s interests or whose activities could bring harm to others.

By booking with us, you may receive occasional promotional emails from us with the ability to opt-out at any time if you choose not to receive them.

**Our Partners**  
Las Vegas Direct has partnered with reputable third parties to offer a variety of products and services. Although we only work with reputable third parties, our business partners’ privacy policies may differ for the privacy policy of LasVegasDirect. We encourage you to review our business partners’ privacy policies to further understand their procedures for collecting, using, and disclosing your information.

**Privacy Changes**  
This privacy policy was created and posted on LasVegasDirect.com on March 12, 2017. LasVegasDirect.com reserves the right to adjust, modify or amend this privacy policy at any time without notice and for any reason. If we decide to change this policy in a material way, we will post notice of the change on our site and notify you via e-mail at the address you have provided. If any changes are unacceptable to you, you may ask that we remove your personal information from our records. We encourage you to periodically review this privacy policy to be informed of how Las Vegas Direct protects your information.

If you have additional questions about the LasVegasDirect.com Privacy Policy, please send us an email at privacy@LasVegasDirect.com.
